

## **EDUCATION**

PUC (H.E.P) -2014
Government Pre University College
B.A. (Bachelor of Arts) -2014-2016
Government College, Hriyuru
Fine Arts Diploma -2020-2021
Reliance Education:
Animation & Visual Effects Institute

### **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**

I have a strong interest in visual arts beyond graphic design. Additionally, I have an interest in interior design, about elements of room decor and enjoy bicycle Ride.

Phone 9686440958

**Email** 

manjunathahyr96@gmail.com

Website

https://www.behance.net/manjunatht2

# **MANJUNATHAT**

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

#### **ABOUT ME**

Creative graphic designer with innovative ideas and a unique approach to visuals. More than 36 months of experience developing designs for print media, online website, Solid understanding of marketing principles and advertising techniques. Great attention to detail and a talent for creating memorable visual designs. Enthusiastic team player who is committed to delivering top results on time and within the budget. Passion for keeping clients satisfied with each project.

## **WORK HISTORY**

2022-2024 Job Position Here.

**Spark International Pvt.Ltd** 

Social Media Poster, Banner, brochure, catalogue, images edited,
Small Video editing

2021-2022 Job Position Here.

Factree Communications Pvt.Ltd.

Poster.Banner.Video Cutting.

2020 - 2021 Job Position Here.

Maverik Facility Management Pvt. Ltd.

Created new design themes for collateral materials. Participated in production of print and social media creatives, promotional web banners, brochure, catalogue, images edited, image composition.

## **SOFTWARE SKILL**

**Adobe Photoshop** 

**Adobe Indesin** 

Adobe Illustrator

**Adobe After effects** 

**Corel Draw** 

**Adobe Premiere Pro**